Alex Smith

620.282.8594 Wichita, KS 67208 Rivero7462@gmail.com

https://www.youtube.com/c/RiveroChannel

GAME DESIGNER

Junior Programmer | Level Designer | 3D Artist

Creative, efficient, and long winded game designer with over three years of experience creating games with C# in Unity. Capable of problem solving and bug testing to get satisfactory results. Expertise in game mechanics, modeling, GUI elements, and asset design.

EXPERIENCE

CETARL Education for All- Wichita, KS

08/2021- PRESENT

Graduate Research Assistant

Responsible for creating a game-based platform for refugee learners, assisting in developing curriculum content for the game, and beta testing the educational platform.

- Successfully created and textured science-based assets with maya.
- Acquired skills necessary to make an engaging learning experience.

Ocarina of Time in Minecraft- Great Bend, KS

05/2013- PRESENT

Game Developer

Created a remake of the game Legend of Zelda Ocarina of Time within Minecraft's game engine.

- Worked on all aspects of its creation such as coding, modeling, and music.
- Achieved over 23,000 downloads within the first year.
- Built a discord server fan base from the ground up with over 1,600 members.

Freelance Videographer- Wichita, KS

10/2021-4/2022

Film and Editor

Filmed and edited three different weddings.

- Made technical decisions regarding elements such as lighting.
- Gained the opportunity to film and edit two more weddings due to recognition from the first.
- Matched music with footage to create a smooth flowing film.

EDUCATION

Wichita State University - Wichita, KS

Bachelor of Arts - Media Arts with Specialization in Game Design, Expected Graduation Date: May, 2023

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Skilled in modeling software such as Maya.
- Capable of reading and typing code in C#.
- Proficient in Adobe products such as Photoshop, Premiere Pro, and After Effects.
- Filmed and edited for three weddings.